[
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "wooden"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      3,
      4,
      5,
      6,
      7
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "table",
      "table",
      "table",
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table"
    ],
    "question_1": "What kind of table is in the house?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0001-1",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "table"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      5,
      17
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "couch",
      "table",
      "window"
    ],
    "question_2": "What is the couch nearest the window placed in front of?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0001-23",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0001_00",
    "new_question": "What type of table is placed in front of the couch near the window?",
    "new_answer": "wooden table",
    "new_answers": [
      "wooden table"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0001_00_mv_0",
    "n_views_can_solve": 3,
    "oracle_views": [
      "600",
      "1460",
      "240",
      "400"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.4563366724476471,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "next to other coffee table surrounded by 2 couches and 2 armchairs"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      6,
      7,
      8,
      9,
      12,
      13
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table",
      "couch",
      "couch",
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where does the coffee table sit in the sitting area?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0001-6",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "tables"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      5,
      6,
      7
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "table",
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table"
    ],
    "question_2": "The couch is on the right of what?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0001-14",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0001_00",
    "new_question": "In the sitting area, what is located to the right of the coffee tables surrounded by 2 couches and 2 armchairs?",
    "new_answer": "couch",
    "new_answers": [
      "couch"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0001_00_mv_15",
    "n_views_can_solve": 2,
    "oracle_views": [
      "620",
      "1460",
      "380"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.7695454002810884,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "brown"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      0,
      1,
      8,
      9
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "couch",
      "couch",
      "couch",
      "couch"
    ],
    "question_1": "What color leather sofa is in the room?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0001-8",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "table"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      5,
      17
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "couch",
      "table",
      "window"
    ],
    "question_2": "What is the couch nearest the window placed in front of?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0001-23",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0001_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the leather couch nearest the window that is placed in front of a table?",
    "new_answer": "brown",
    "new_answers": [
      "brown"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0001_00_mv_2",
    "n_views_can_solve": 3,
    "oracle_views": [
      "600",
      "1460",
      "320",
      "420"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.3978029669946032,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "brown couch"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      6,
      9
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "coffee table",
      "couch"
    ],
    "question_1": "The coffee table on the right is closest to what?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0001-7",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "to right of picture"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      6,
      7
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the coffee table lying?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0001-12",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0001_00",
    "new_question": "What is next to the coffee table that is located on the right side of the picture?",
    "new_answer": "brown couch",
    "new_answers": [
      "brown couch"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0001_00_mv_10",
    "n_views_can_solve": 0,
    "oracle_views": [
      "620"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 1.0,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 1.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "next to other coffee table surrounded by 2 couches and 2 armchairs"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      6,
      7,
      8,
      9,
      12,
      13
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table",
      "couch",
      "couch",
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where does the coffee table sit in the sitting area?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0001-6",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "brown"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      1,
      8,
      9
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "couch",
      "couch",
      "couch",
      "couch"
    ],
    "question_2": "What color leather sofa is in the room?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0001-8",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0001_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the leather sofa in the sitting area with two coffee tables surrounded by 2 couches and 2 armchairs?",
    "new_answer": "brown",
    "new_answers": [
      "brown"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0001_00_mv_17",
    "n_views_can_solve": 3,
    "oracle_views": [
      "600",
      "1460",
      "300",
      "420"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.6733522252459523,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "brown couch"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      6,
      9
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "coffee table",
      "couch"
    ],
    "question_1": "The coffee table on the right is closest to what?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0001-7",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "brown"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      6,
      7
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table"
    ],
    "question_2": "What's the color of the coffee tables in the room?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0001-18",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0001_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the coffee table on the right that is closest to the brown couch?",
    "new_answer": "brown",
    "new_answers": [
      "brown"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0001_00_mv_20",
    "n_views_can_solve": 0,
    "oracle_views": [
      "620"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 1.0,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 1.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "tables"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      5,
      6,
      7
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "table",
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table"
    ],
    "question_1": "The couch is on the right of what?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0001-14",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0001_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      6,
      7,
      12
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "coffee table",
      "coffee table",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_2": "How many tables is the brown armchair facing?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0001-15",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0001_00",
    "new_question": "How many tables are on the right side of the couch that the brown armchair is facing?",
    "new_answer": "2 tables",
    "new_answers": [
      "2 tables"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0001_00_mv_16",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "620",
      "380"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.75,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "left of refrigerator",
      "on wall left of refrigerator",
      "above sink"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      10,
      14
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "refrigerator",
      "soap dispenser"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where is the soap dispenser located?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0003-7",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "above refrigerator",
      "above kitchen counter"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      4,
      10
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "cabinet",
      "refrigerator"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the cabinet located?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0003-71",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0003_00",
    "new_question": "What is located to the left of the refrigerator where the cabinet is also positioned?",
    "new_answer": "soap dispenser",
    "new_answers": [
      "soap dispenser"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0003_00_mv_3",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "760",
      "420"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.587321006263316,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.31068692005346477,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "right of long kitchen cabinets",
      "in corner on right"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      5,
      10
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "kitchen cabinets",
      "refrigerator"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where is the black silver fridge located?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0003-9",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "refrigerator",
      "water cooler"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      7,
      10
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "water cooler",
      "refrigerator"
    ],
    "question_2": "What type of cooler is next to a cabinet?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0003-21",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0003_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the refrigerator located to the right of the long kitchen cabinets?",
    "new_answer": "black silver",
    "new_answers": [
      "black silver"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0003_00_mv_5",
    "n_views_can_solve": 2,
    "oracle_views": [
      "500",
      "760",
      "40"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.33318412832290534,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 0.999552384968716
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "refrigerator",
      "water cooler"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      7,
      10
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "water cooler",
      "refrigerator"
    ],
    "question_1": "What type of cooler is next to a cabinet?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0003-21",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "above refrigerator",
      "above kitchen counter"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      4,
      10
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "cabinet",
      "refrigerator"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the cabinet located?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0003-71",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0003_00",
    "new_question": "What type of cooler is located next to the cabinet that is above the refrigerator?",
    "new_answer": "water cooler",
    "new_answers": [
      "water cooler"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0003_00_mv_4",
    "n_views_can_solve": 2,
    "oracle_views": [
      "760",
      "40",
      "420"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.3333333333333333,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "left of refrigerator",
      "on wall left of refrigerator",
      "above sink"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      10,
      14
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "refrigerator",
      "soap dispenser"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where is the soap dispenser located?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0003-7",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0003_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "right of long kitchen cabinets",
      "in corner on right"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      5,
      10
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "kitchen cabinets",
      "refrigerator"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the black silver fridge located?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0003-9",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0003_00",
    "new_question": "In which direction is the soap dispenser located relative to the black silver fridge that is right of the long kitchen cabinets?",
    "new_answer": "left of refrigerator",
    "new_answers": [
      "left of refrigerator"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0003_00_mv_0",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "500",
      "760"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5740899386261676,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.45155689519863995,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0004_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "3"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      5,
      10,
      11
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "chair",
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many chairs are next to each other?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0004-32",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0004_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "against wall",
      "against wall"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      5,
      9
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the blue and grey chair placed?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0004-45",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0004_00",
    "new_question": "How many chairs are next to each other that are against the wall?",
    "new_answer": "3 chairs",
    "new_answers": [
      "3 chairs"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0004_00_mv_0",
    "n_views_can_solve": 0,
    "oracle_views": [
      "100"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.9160857945041232,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.7746320525720534,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0004_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "against wall"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      5,
      10,
      11
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "chair",
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_1": "How is the gray and blue leather chair placed?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0004-4",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0004_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "against wall",
      "against wall"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      5,
      9
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the blue and grey chair placed?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0004-45",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0004_00",
    "new_question": "What is the placement of the chair that is both gray and blue in color?",
    "new_answer": "against wall",
    "new_answers": [
      "against wall"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0004_00_mv_2",
    "n_views_can_solve": 0,
    "oracle_views": [
      "100"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.9160857945041232,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.7746320525720534,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0004_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "against wall"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      5,
      10,
      11
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "chair",
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_1": "How is the gray and blue leather chair placed next to other identical chairs?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0004-10",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0004_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "against wall",
      "against wall"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      5,
      9
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the blue and grey chair placed?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0004-45",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0004_00",
    "new_question": "What is the placement of the gray and blue leather chair among the other identical chairs?",
    "new_answer": "against wall",
    "new_answers": [
      "against wall"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0004_00_mv_1",
    "n_views_can_solve": 0,
    "oracle_views": [
      "100"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.9160857945041232,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.7746320525720534,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0005_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "at table",
      "at table",
      "at table",
      "at table",
      "pushed under desk",
      "under table"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      9,
      10,
      16
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "table",
      "table",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where is the green chair located?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0005-9",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0005_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      5,
      16
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_2": "How many green chairs does the brown table face?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0005-36",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0005_00",
    "new_question": "How many green chairs are located at the table?",
    "new_answer": "2 green chairs",
    "new_answers": [
      "2 green chairs"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0005_00_mv_1",
    "n_views_can_solve": 0,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1120"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.9871599745074193,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.9618586258539926,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0005_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "at table",
      "at table",
      "at table",
      "at table",
      "pushed under desk",
      "under table"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      9,
      10,
      16
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "table",
      "table",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where is the green chair located?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0005-9",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0005_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "green",
      "green plastic armchair",
      "green desk",
      "green desk"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      5,
      16
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "chair",
      "chair"
    ],
    "question_2": "What type of chair is facing a table?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0005-14",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0005_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the chair that is located at a table and facing another table?",
    "new_answer": "green",
    "new_answers": [
      "green"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0005_00_mv_0",
    "n_views_can_solve": 0,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1120"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.9871599745074193,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.9618586258539926,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "on windows",
      "in middle",
      "right of bed",
      "right of bed",
      "in front of window",
      "in left corner of room"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      1,
      3,
      31
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "bed",
      "curtain",
      "curtain"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where is the curtain located?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0006-121",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "beds"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      1,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "bed",
      "bed"
    ],
    "question_2": "What can be seen parallel to the wall?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0006-127",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0006_00",
    "new_question": "On which side of the beds that are parallel to the wall are the curtains located?",
    "new_answer": "right of bed or in right corner of room",
    "new_answers": [
      "right of bed",
      "in right corner of room"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0006_00_mv_4",
    "n_views_can_solve": 2,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1560",
      "1220",
      "1260"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5650224737811127,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      11,
      12
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_1": "What is placed up to another pillow?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0006-16",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "white",
      "white"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      12,
      17
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_2": "What color is the pillow on the bed?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0006-61",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0006_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the pillow placed up to another pillow on the bed?",
    "new_answer": "white",
    "new_answers": [
      "white"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0006_00_mv_5",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1280",
      "1640"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.7649918664585984,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.2949755993757951,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "8"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      10,
      11,
      17,
      18
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many white pillows are there?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0006-1",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "left",
      "head"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      12,
      17,
      18
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_2": "On what side of the bed is the white pillow on?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0006-71",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0006_00",
    "new_question": "How many white pillows are located on the left or head side of the bed?",
    "new_answer": "8 white pillows are on the left or head side of the bed",
    "new_answers": [
      "8 white pillows are on the left",
      "head side of the bed"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0006_00_mv_0",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1400",
      "1660"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.6533839649025269,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.14689568331609434,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "8"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      10,
      11,
      17,
      18
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many white pillows are there?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0006-1",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "right",
      "left"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      12,
      17
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_2": "On what side of the bed is the white pillow located?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0006-79",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0006_00",
    "new_question": "How many white pillows are located on either the right or left side of the bed?",
    "new_answer": "8 white pillows",
    "new_answers": [
      "8 white pillows"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0006_00_mv_11",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1400",
      "1660"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.6533839649025269,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.14689568331609434,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "8"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      10,
      11,
      17,
      18
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many white pillows are there?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0006-1",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      11,
      12
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_2": "What is placed up to another pillow?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0006-16",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0006_00",
    "new_question": "How many white pillows are placed next to another pillow?",
    "new_answer": "at least 2 white pillows",
    "new_answers": [
      "at least 2 white pillows"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0006_00_mv_1",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1400",
      "1660"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.6533839649025269,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.14689568331609434,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "8"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      10,
      11,
      17,
      18
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many white pillows are there?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0006-1",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0006_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "white",
      "white"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      12,
      17
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "pillow",
      "pillow"
    ],
    "question_2": "What color is the pillow on the bed?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0006-61",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0006_00",
    "new_question": "How many white pillows are on the bed?",
    "new_answer": "8 white pillows are on the bed",
    "new_answers": [
      "8 white pillows are on the bed"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0006_00_mv_6",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1400",
      "1660"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.6533839649025269,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.14689568331609434,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000002
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "whole"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      0,
      1,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "What part of the chair is brown?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0013-22",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      3
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_2": "How many brown woods are above the table?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0013-33",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0013_00",
    "new_question": "How many brown chairs are located above the table?",
    "new_answer": "2 brown chairs",
    "new_answers": [
      "2 brown chairs"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0013_00_mv_4",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "20",
      "580"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5299120276153392,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.010183755091558482,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      0,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many chairs are on the right?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0013-9",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2 armchairs"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      1,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_2": "What is the coffee table in front of?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0013-19",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0013_00",
    "new_question": "How many chairs are on the right side that are in front of the coffee table?",
    "new_answer": "2 armchairs",
    "new_answers": [
      "2 armchairs"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0013_00_mv_3",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "580",
      "320"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.4842536782283597,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.018874758481744355,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      0,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many chairs are on the right?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0013-9",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      3
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_2": "How many brown woods are above the table?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0013-33",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0013_00",
    "new_question": "How many brown chairs are on the right side of the table?",
    "new_answer": "2 brown chairs",
    "new_answers": [
      "2 brown chairs"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0013_00_mv_5",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "600",
      "20"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.633611862604706,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.010183755091558482,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "beige"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      0,
      1,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "What color is the cotton armchair?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0013-12",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      3
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_2": "How many brown woods are above the table?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0013-33",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0013_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the cotton armchair located near the 2 brown woods above the table?",
    "new_answer": "beige",
    "new_answers": [
      "beige"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0013_00_mv_0",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "20",
      "580"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5299120276153392,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.010183755091558482,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "brown"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      0,
      1,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "What color is the chair?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0013-21",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      3
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_2": "How many brown woods are above the table?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0013-33",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0013_00",
    "new_question": "How many brown chairs are above the table?",
    "new_answer": "2 brown chairs",
    "new_answers": [
      "2 brown chairs"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0013_00_mv_1",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "20",
      "580"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5299120276153392,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.010183755091558482,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "3"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      0,
      1,
      2
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_1": "How many chairs are around the coffee table?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0013-15",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0013_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "2"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      0,
      3
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "armchair",
      "armchair"
    ],
    "question_2": "How many brown woods are above the table?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0013-33",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0013_00",
    "new_question": "How many chairs are around the coffee table that have brown wood above them?",
    "new_answer": "2 chairs",
    "new_answers": [
      "2 chairs"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0013_00_mv_2",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "20",
      "580"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5299120276153392,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.010183755091558482,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "towels"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      8,
      15,
      19
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "toilet",
      "towel",
      "towel"
    ],
    "question_1": "What is above the toilet?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0029-12",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "cream",
      "cream"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      18,
      19
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "towel",
      "towel"
    ],
    "question_2": "What color is the towel, on the left, hanging from the rack. above the toilet?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0029-68",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0029_00",
    "new_question": "What color is the towel located on the left side of the rack above the toilet?",
    "new_answer": "cream",
    "new_answers": [
      "cream"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0029_00_mv_10",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1900",
      "160"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.6967442938108439,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000004
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "on wall mounted shelf above toilet"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      8,
      16,
      18
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "toilet",
      "towel",
      "towel"
    ],
    "question_1": "Where are the folded towels located?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0029-69",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "right of shower curtain"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      1,
      8
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "shower curtain",
      "toilet"
    ],
    "question_2": "Where is the towel kept?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0029-94",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0029_00",
    "new_question": "Where are the folded towels located relative to the shower curtain?",
    "new_answer": "on wall mounted shelf above toilet, which is to the right of the shower curtain",
    "new_answers": [
      "on wall mounted shelf above toilet, which is to the right of the shower curtain"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0029_00_mv_49",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1900",
      "140"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "towels"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      8,
      15,
      19
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "toilet",
      "towel",
      "towel"
    ],
    "question_1": "What is next to the toilet bowl?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0029-25",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "cream",
      "cream"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      18,
      19
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "towel",
      "towel"
    ],
    "question_2": "What color is the towel, on the left, hanging from the rack. above the toilet?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0029-68",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0029_00",
    "new_question": "What color are the towels located next to the toilet bowl?",
    "new_answer": "cream",
    "new_answers": [
      "cream"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0029_00_mv_76",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1900",
      "160"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.6967442938108439,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000004
  },
  {
    "scene_id": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_1": [
      "metallic trash can"
    ],
    "object_ids_1": [
      1,
      6,
      8
    ],
    "object_names_1": [
      "shower curtain",
      "trash can",
      "toilet"
    ],
    "question_1": "What is in between a toilet and shower curtain?",
    "question_id_1": "train-scene0029-2",
    "scene_id_1": "scene0029_00",
    "answers_2": [
      "towels"
    ],
    "object_ids_2": [
      8,
      15,
      19
    ],
    "object_names_2": [
      "toilet",
      "towel",
      "towel"
    ],
    "question_2": "What is above the toilet?",
    "question_id_2": "train-scene0029-12",
    "scene_id_2": "scene0029_00",
    "new_question": "What is located between the toilet and shower curtain, directly below the towels?",
    "new_answer": "metallic trash can",
    "new_answers": [
      "metallic trash can"
    ],
    "question_id": "scene0029_00_mv_50",
    "n_views_can_solve": 1,
    "oracle_views": [
      "1900",
      "100"
    ],
    "best_view_overlap_mean": 0.5856640987411115,
    "best_view_overlap_min": 0.0,
    "best_view_overlap_max": 1.0000000000000004
  }
]